<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BugBazaar</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open Drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close Drawer</string>
    <string name="my_profile">My Profile</string>
    <!-- Items Description -->
    <string name="desc_camera">Introducing the "Old Town Camera" – because capturing memories is like fine wine, it gets better with age! This vintage-inspired camera comes with a built-in time machine feature that instantly transports you to the golden days of photography. Say cheese and embark on a nostalgic journey with a touch of retro flair. Warning: May cause sudden urges to dig out old photo albums and reminisce about the good ol days of black and white snapshots. Handle with care, memories included!</string>

    <string name="desc_watch">Meet the "Dumb Watch" – because who needs smart when you can have simple sophistication strapped to your wrist? This watch is so dumb, it wont remind you of your unread emails, track your heartbeat, or tell you the weather. Instead, it excels at timeless features like ticking and looking stylish. No apps, no notifications, just good ol hours and minutes doing their thing. Perfect for those who believe in making their own time, without any unnecessary intelligence getting in the way. Dumb never looked so good!</string>

    <string name="desc_cycle">Introducing the "Lazy Bicycle," the two-wheeled marvel that understands your need for speed... or lack thereof. Engineered for those who prefer a leisurely cruise over a heart-pounding race, this bike comes with an exclusive Snail Mode for an extra-slow, ultra-relaxed journey. Equipped with a state-of-the-art No Rush Technology, our Lazy Bicycle ensures you arrive exactly when you feel like it, offering a new level of two-wheeled tranquility. So, grab a seat, pedal at your own pace, and let the Lazy Bicycle redefine the art of moving slow and looking cool.</string>

    <string name="desc_skateboard">Introducing the "Skate-Board," your ultimate vehicle for pretending youre an effortlessly cool sidewalk surfer without the risk of face-planting. Designed for those who dream of shredding like a pro but reality-check themselves before attempting an ollie. Our board comes with advanced features like wobbly balance and unexpected stops, providing an authentic experience that perfectly mimics your attempts at looking rad. So grab your Skate-Board, hit the pavement, and remember: its not about the tricks you land, but the laughs you share when you cant.</string>

    <string name="desc_iphone">Peel away the competition with this tropical tech treat. It’s not just a phone; its a deliciously juicy experience. Loaded with essential vitamins, this Pineapple iPhone is your daily dose of sweetness. Worried about battery life? Dont be! It comes with the unique "Charged by Sunshine" feature. Just leave it in the sun for an hour, and voila – your phone is charged and ready to bring a taste of the tropics to your tech life. Get yours now and join the fruity revolution – because calling should be as refreshing as a sip of piña colada on a beach!</string>

    <string name="desc_controller">Meet the Z Box Gaming Computer – where gaming meets intergalactic adventure! This computer is so powerful; its like having a black hole of entertainment right on your desk. Need a break from reality? Dive into a gaming experience so immersive; you might forget where you left your spaceship keys. The Z Box is not just a computer; its a portal to alternate universes where your high scores are celebrated across the cosmos. Worried about lag? Fear not! Our advanced Warp Speed Processing ensures that even in the far reaches of the gaming galaxy, your commands are executed at the speed of light. Upgrade your gaming experience to light speed with the Z Box – because conquering virtual worlds is a universal pastime!</string>

    <string name="desc_rat">The computer mouse thats so swift, even cats envy its agility! This mouse is so sleek and fast; it makes ordinary mice look like theyre stuck in slow motion. Equipped with "Stealth Whisker Technology," the HyperClick 3000 lets you navigate through cyberspace with the grace of a ninja cat. Worried about accidental clicks? Fear not! Our "Anti-Pawprint" design ensures that even the most curious feline friends wont leave their mark. The HyperClick 3000: Because your digital adventures deserve a mouse thats purr-fectly fast and fur-iously fun!</string>

    <string name="desc_tws">WhisperWear X3: The TWS that even secret agents use when theyre off duty. These earbuds are so discreet; they make ninjas sound like a marching band. With our SilentBeat Technology, you can enjoy your favorite tunes at a volume that wont wake a sleeping cat. Worried about someone overhearing your top-secret playlist? Fear not! The WhisperWear X3 comes with StealthSound mode, ensuring that your music remains classified. Get ready for an eargasm of espionage with WhisperWear X3 – Shhh, its a secret!</string>

    <string name="desc_skullphone">Skull Symphony Headphones: When you put these on, its not just music; its a bone-shaking experience. Our headphones are so immersive; youll think youre in a rock concert inside a haunted mansion. With our patented SpookyBass Technology, you can feel the beats in your bones—literally. The Skull Symphony Headphones: because sometimes, you just need a little extra skeleton in your playlist. Warning: May cause involuntary headbanging and a sudden urge to dance like a skeleton.</string>

    <string name="desc_macbook">MacN CheeseBook Air: The only laptop that combines the elegance of a MacBook with the comfort of a warm bowl of mac n cheese. Our keyboard is so buttery smooth that typing feels like stirring melted cheese into perfectly cooked pasta. Equipped with the latest Cheesy Chip processor, this laptop is your recipe for success. With a display so crisp, you can practically taste the pixels. The MacN CheeseBook Air: because creativity is best served with a side of cheddar!</string>

    <string name="desc_trimmer">Useless Trimmer: For those who want a clean shave from reality but end up with a messy beard of disappointment. Our trimmer comes with a built-in confusion sensor that ensures you will never get the style you intended. With blades as sharp as your last breakup and a battery life shorter than your attention span, the Useless Trimmer is the perfect companion for a grooming routine thats as unpredictable as life itself. Warning: May cause existential beard crises.</string>

    <!---->
    <string name="hardc0d3d_passw0rd">BugBazaarSeccool</string>

</resources>